Imaad Karim

A3/A Wing, Flat No 62 Ravi Park Society Wanowrie Jagtap Chowk Pune - 411040 +91 8605842287 imaadk90@gmail.com

SKILLS

Excellent communications skills along with years of experience in Bpo And non Bpo Industry for the last 8 years, combined with the know how to tackle situations and processes of any nature and provide a resolution to the same. Target driven, Career oriented and an undying and professional approach towards career goals and achievements combined with dedication towards achieving and working under the guidelines of the organization along with the strive for growth and the zeal to yield best results as per the businesses requirements.

EDUCATION

NIOS, Pune — *H.S.C*

2007

NIOS, Pune — S.S.C

2005

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi & Marathi.

EXPERIENCE

TechMbs LTD.

Sept 2020 - Present

Currently working as an advisor in the customer relations / complaints team for a network provider based in the UK. KPI's include Net promoter score, Average handling time, Resolution and compliance. Primary responsibilities include resolving a customers query end to end as a part of an escalation team encompassing multiple vertices of the business so as to provide a resolution to the customers complaint.

FLG Caterers.

Nov2017 - Setp 2020

Worked as a restaurant manager for a local food joint. Primary responsibilities including managing workers, accounting, inventory management and employee lifecycle/roster management. Alo included secondary responsibilities like Marketing, Branding strategies, processing third party orders via food apps, etc.

TechMbs LTD.

Oct 2016 - Nov 2017

Worked as an advisor for a UK based telecom company in multiple portfolios, including sales, retentions and customer services. Key roles included retaining current and acquiring new customer in a target based environment adhering to deadlines.. Providing end to end resolution to multi skill set queries by consulting other departments. Getting trained on and implementing new tools and process updates on a timely basis. Analysis of Churn or loss and strategizing churn management. Exposure to and updation of multiple softwares, to achieve results.

Credence Resource Management — CSR

Aug 2015 - October 2016

Worked as a debt collector in the final stage of collections, collecting past due bills that are pending for over a year. Key Roles include presenting customers with options such as monthly payments or settlements in order to have their bills resolved. Also Providing other information about the bill and services used, charges and auxiliary information. Secondary roles included verifying payments made by consumers, handling call escalations and back end work such as forwarding requests for emails or letters to be dispatched to consumers and account tagging and processing.

Psycle Events — Event Coordinator

Dec 2009 - June 2015

Key roles Included managing artists and venues in order to see through and execute events. To scout for new and upcoming artists and venues across the country. To conceptualize and deliver events as per the company and clients visions. To market events via various platforms such as Facebook, twitter, bookmyshow and other marketing mediums.